Guide to the New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia MC.234
New York University Archives
- Series II: Complex Pig Figurines and Sets
  - Subseries II B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Humans
    - Woman with Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 17)
      Ceramic woman in blue holding a white pig and with two white pigs at her feet; figure shattered
    - Girl in Bonnet with Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 4)
      Girl wearing pink and blue bonnet with three pink pigs, one larger than the others; ceramic
    - Boy with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 16)
      Boy in traditional German garb with ball and stick with pig and sign that reads "Aurora" with bird
    - Child with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 5)
      Naked child with gold pig; ceramic
    - Boy with Pig in Outhouse, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 3)
      Boy walking in on pig using an outhouse; ceramic
    - Woman Riding Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 14)
      Bobble head woman dressed in blue riding a pink pig; metal and ceramic
    - Child with Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 2)
      Child in white holding a spotted pig
    - People and Animals in Wood, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 2)
      Two men and one woman in tending to cows, a pig, and a basket of eggs in a wooded area; ceramic
    - Boy Riding Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 7)
      Boy in black with ladder, clock, and note riding a beige pig; ceramic
    - Woman Holding Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 27)
      Woman with curls in bonnet, teal dress, and apron holding a very light pink pig; ceramic
    - Boy with Knife and Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 3)
      Boy dressed in shirt, shorts, an apron, and a blue hat carrying a knife and pig; ceramic
    - Boy in Colorful Outfit with Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 12)
      Boy in multi-colored outfit with two off-white and blue pigs at his feet; ceramic
    - Boy in Overalls Riding Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 2)
      Boy in overalls riding a pink pig; ceramic; boy's head has detached
    - Man with Pig at Feet, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 7)
      Man in brown outfit with sack and umbrella with white pig at his feet; ceramic
    - White Child Riding Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 55)
      White child riding a white pig; ceramic; paint loss
    - Chef Holding Pigs Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 10)
      Ceramic man in chef's uniform with apron that reads "menu" holding two white pigs; set of two. Related to item 9 in box 5.
  - Subseries II C: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Human-Like Traits
    This subseries contains multiple pig figurines or sets of pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of ceramic material. The figurines are engaged in some sort of human-like activity or display human-like behavior.
    - Pigs with Wine Bottles, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 8)
      Two white, ceramic pigs with white wine bottles
    - Pigs in a Sleigh, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 17)
      Ceramic figurine of two white pigs riding a blue sleigh
    - Pigs Holding Bouquets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 9, 19-20)
      Set of three ceramic, pink, sitting pigs with large smiles holding colorful bouquets of flowers; damaged
    - Pigs Separated by Telephone Booth, circa 1900-2013 (Box 4, Item 11)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs separated by a green telephone booth
    - Set of Two Sows with Piglets in Pram, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 19)
      Ceramic, fox-like sow pushing her piglet in a yellow pram; set of two. Related to box 18 item 28.
    - Set of Standing Pigs with Bows, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 7, 18-19)
      Set of hot pink, ceramic pigs sitting upright, and wearing bright, green bows around their necks; some chips in ceramic
    - Pigs in a Canoe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 13)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs with white hats rowing a canoe
    - Sow with Piglet and Rabbit at Washtub Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 15)
      Sow holding swaddled piglet with rabbit by washtub that reads "Was Not Happy Until He Got It;" set of two ceramic figurines related to box 6 item 20.
    - Pigs in Boat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 10)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs in a green boat with gold detail
    - Pink Pigs in Car, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 10)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs in dark green car
    - Pink and Green Pigs in Car, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 14)
      One pink and one green pig in green car; ceramic
    - Tan Pigs in Car, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 16)
      Two tan, ceramic pigs in green car
    - Pig Pushing a Cart of Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 4)
      White, ceramic pig pushing a cart with clover wheels carrying three piglets; cart reads "The More, The Merrier"
    - Set of Pigs in Plum Coats, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 17)
      Ceramic pigs in plum coats, blue vests, and red hats; set of two. Related to box 13 item 24.
    - Pigs Playing Pool, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 2)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs playing pool
    - Pigs by Fireplace, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 3)
      Three ceramic pigs in orange and white clothing in front of a fireplace
    - Pig Pumping Water for Other Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 15)
      Off-white pig pumping water for four other white pigs; ceramic
    - Pigs and Telephone, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 23)
      One pig outside and one pig inside public telephone box; the text "engaged" appears at the bottom; ceramic
    - Pig with Piglet in Stroller, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 21)
      White pig with white piglet in stroller with an inscription that reads "Hushabyebaby, Don't You Cry, You'll Be A Sausage, Bye and Bye"
    - Pigs Holding Trotters in Car, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 22)
      Two, pink pigs holding trotters in a green car; ceramic
    - Pig and Piglet in Boat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 2)
      Pink pig and piglet with blue hat in boat; faded inscription; ceramic
    - Gold Pigs in Car, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 6)
      Two gold pigs holding trotters in a yellowish-green, car; ceramic
    - Beige Pigs Playing Instruments, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 65-69)
      Light beige, ceramic pigs playing instruments
    - Yellow Pigs in a Band, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 24-27)
      Yellowish pigs playing instruments in a band; ceramic
    - Set of Two Sows with Piglets in Pram, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 28)
      Set of two pink sows with piglets in pram
    - Set of Pigs in Plum Coats, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 24)
      Ceramic pigs in plum coats, blue vests, and red hats; set of two related to box 9 item 17.
    - Sow with Piglet and Rabbit at Washtub Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 20)
      Sow holding swaddled piglet with rabbit by washtub that says "Was Not Happy Until He Got It;" set of two ceramic figurines related to box 27 item 15.
  - Subseries II D: Glass, Stone, and Plastic Pig Sets
    This subseries contains multiple pig figurines or sets of pig figurines made of glass, stone, or plastic.
    - Beige Pig Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 16-17)
      Set of two beige, plastic pigs
    - Reddish-Brown Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 15-16)
      Set of two reddish-brown stone pigs standing
    - Nesting Glass Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 1)
      Three clear, glass pigs nesting within each other
    - Dark Blue, Glass Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 7-8)
      Set of two dark blue, glass pigs; missing limbs
  - Subseries II E: Wooden Pig Sets
    This subseries contains multiple pig figurines or sets of pig figurines made of wood.
    - Nesting Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 13)
      Nesting, wooden pigs with clover motif
    - Sow with Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 8)
      Brown, wooden sow nursing her piglets
    - Man with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 56)
      Wooden scene of man with bucket cutting a pig with a knife; parts have started to detach
    - Wooden Pig Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 86-100)
      Set of sixteen wooden pigs in various positions and sizes some damaged
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 28)
      Small wooden pig painted pink; paint losses. Part of a set of five pigs in Box 17 items 30-33.
  - Subseries II F: Metal Pig Sets
    This subseries contains multiple pig figurines or sets of pig figurines made of metal.
    - Sow Feeding Her Young, circa 1900-2013 (Box 3, Item 5)
      Metal figurine of sow nursing her piglets
    - Bronze-Colored Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 6)
      Three bronze-colored, metal pigs standing next to each other
    - Boy Holding Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 9)
      Bronze-colored boy holding a pig in each arm
    - Pigs in Shed, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 10)
      Metal shed with latch door revealing two pink pigs
    - Boy and Pig on Platform, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 7)
      Bronze-colored boy in hat, coat, and britches on a stone with a leaping pig; all on a platform; metal
    - Devil Like Figure Riding a Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 23)
      Red devil-like figure riding an off-white pig; metal
    - Set of Black, Metal Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 32, 44)
      Metal pigs painted black and in a standing position
- Series III: Utilitarian Objects
  This series contains objects with an intended function or use, including ashtrays, kitchenware, piggy banks, children's toys, Christmas ornaments, jewelry containers, buckets, candle holders, thermometers, measuring tapes, and pencil and paint brush holders. These objects are pig shaped, include three-dimensional ornamentation of one or several pigs, or are adorned with a flat pig motif.
  - Subseries III A: Ashtrays
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed ashtrays in varied materials.
    - Pig on Horseshoe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 12)
      White, ceramic pig with beige detail on white horseshoe-shaped platform with clover and note detail
    - Pigs Sitting Along Ashtray Edge, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 2)
      Three pink, ceramic pigs sitting along green and orange ashtray edge
    - Pig in Hat Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 8)
      Ceramic, human-like pig in gray fisher hat and red kerchief
    - Sleeping Pig Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 7)
      Ceramic, sleeping, pink pig along blue ashtray; broken ear
    - Pigs in Field Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 5)
      Ceramic ashtray showing two light gray pigs and one black pig in a field; text reads "Three of a Kind"
    - Pig in Suit on Leaf-Shaped Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 4)
      Ceramic pig in top hat and colorful suit in oversized, leaf-shaped ashtray
    - Gray Pig Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 1)
      Grayish, metal ashtray with pig
    - Pig on Lily Pad Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 3)
      Pink, ceramic pig on lily pad or in water ashtray
    - White Pigs and Blue Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 5)
      Three light gray or off-white pigs with blue ashtray and cigarette; ceramic ashtray
    - Pig Ear-Shaped Ashtray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 35)
      Flesh-colored, pig ear-shaped ashtray
  - Subseries III B: Salt and Pepper Shakers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed salt and pepper shakers in varied materials.
    - Black Pig-Shaped Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 12)
      Black, pig-shaped, ceramic shaker with bright pink nose
    - Reddish-Brown Pig-Shaped Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 5)
      Reddish-brown, wooden, pig-shaped shaker with red, open mouth and prominent eyelashes; bottom cork missing
    - Pig in Hat and Bowtie Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 19)
      Colorful, ceramic shaker of pig wearing a green hat and bowtie
    - Set of Pigs with Flowers and Jewels for Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 21)
      Set of purple and pink, ceramic pigs with flowers on back shakers; jewels for eyes. Related to box 17 item 16.
    - Porky Pig Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 7)
      Shaker shaped like Porky Pig in a blue suit coat, pink vest, and green bow tie carrying a hammer
    - Pig with Flowers on Head Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 14)
      Ceramic, delicate, pink, pig-shaped shaker with prominent eyelashes and flowers on head
    - Chef Pig Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 15)
      Ceramic shaker of a beige pig in white chef hat and apron reading a cookbook
    - Chef Pig with Ladle Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 11)
      Ceramic shaker of a pig in a chef apron and hat with a ladle
    - Pink and Black Pig Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 16)
      Ceramic shaker of black pig with hot pink snout and ears
    - Gold Pig Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 11)
      Gold-colored, metal pig shaker
    - Set of Pigs in Overalls Shakers, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 15, 18)
      Set shakers of pigs in overalls and orange hats
    - Pink Pig Shaker, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 48)
      Pink, ceramic pig shaker
    - Set of Pigs with Flowers and Jewels for Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 16)
      Set of purple and pink, ceramic pigs with flowers on back shakers; jewels for eyes. Related to box 11 item 21.
  - Subseries III C: Gravy Boats, Salad Dressing Bottles, and Creamers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed gravy boats, salad dressing bottles, and creamers in varied materials.
    - Pig in Chef Outfit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 4)
      Ceramic creamer container in the shape of a human-like pig wearing a white chef uniform and carrying a yellow ladle
    - Pork Dripping Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 13)
      Off-white, ceramic, pig-shaped container with brown lid that reads "pork dripping"
    - Salad Dressing Bottle with Pig Face Base, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 2)
      White, ceramic salad dressing bottle with stopper and pink pig face at base
    - Brown Bottle with Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 30)
      "Viel Glück" brown, ceramic bottle with pink pig
    - Brown Pig Bottle, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 27)
      Brown, ceramic bottle with pig. "Camark" stamp on bottom
  - Subseries III D: Pitchers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed pitchers in varied materials.
    - Beige Pig Pitcher, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 8)
      Beige, ceramic, pig-shaped pitcher
    - Blushing Pig Pitcher, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 1)
      Beige and black, pig-shaped, ceramic pitcher with rosy cheeks
    - Set of Spotted Pig Pitchers, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 1)
      Pink and black spotted, ceramic, pig-shaped pitchers; one has tape residue. Related to box 16 item 6.
    - White, Blue, and Brown Pig Pitcher, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 4)
      Off-white, ceramic, pig-shaped pitcher with blue and brown detail
    - Set of Spotted Pig Pitchers, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 6)
      Pink and black spotted, ceramic, pig-shaped pitchers; one has tape residue. Related to box 8 item 1.
  - Subseries III E: Beer Mugs, Shot Glasses, and Wine Openers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed beer mugs, shot glasses, and wine openers in varied materials.
    - Shot Glass with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 26)
      Clear, glass shot glass with a white pig and the word "Gentlemen"
    - Pig-Shaped Beer Stein, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 3)
      Beige, ceramic, pig-shaped beer stein with metal handle and text that reads "Viel Schwein Viel Glück;" chips in ceramic
    - Pig-Shaped Wine Opener, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 1)
      Metal, pig-shaped bottle opener
    - Beige Pig Beer Stein, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 22)
      Ceramic beer stein shaped like a beige pig with coat of arms on a platform; metal handle
    - Series of Shot Glasses with Pig Faces, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 79-82)
      Set of white, ceramic shot glasses with pig faces
  - Subseries III F: Plates, Cups, and Cookie Cutters
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed plates, cups, and cookie cutters in varied materials.
    - Cup with Pig Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 9)
      White, ceramic cup with red pig motif
    - Cochon Plate, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 20)
      Ceramic plate that reads "Flowers for Bees Restaurant, Au Pied de Cochon, Candies for Ladies"; pig in a chef uniform in the middle of the plate
    - Pig-Shaped Cookie Cutter, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 36)
      Metal, pig-shaped cookie cutter
  - Subseries III G: Cookie Jars and Other Food Containers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed cookie jars and food containers in varied materials.
    - Pig with Clover Motif Eating an Apple, circa 1900-2013 (Box 4, Item 2)
      White, ceramic, pig-shaped container; pig has a clover motif all over body and is eating an apple; apple handle
    - Pig in Suit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 5)
      Ceramic food container shaped like a pig in suit carrying a sword
    - Pig Smoking, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 1)
      Beige, ceramic pig head with blue hair smoking; bottom of cookie jar missing; chips in ceramic
    - Pig in Traditional German Garb Smoking, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 19)
      Pig in traditional German garb smoking a pipe; ceramic container
    - Pig Head Bowl, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 5)
      Ceramic, pig head-shaped bowl that is tan and brown in color
    - Pig Head Container with Collar and Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 14)
      Ceramic, cookie jar in the shape of a blue pig head with black hat and polka dot collar; tape residue present
  - Subseries III H: Piggy Banks
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed piggy banks in varied materials.
    - Christmas Piggy Bank, 1946 (Box 26, Item 27)
      Christmas piggy bank in the form of a card that opens with slots to hold coins
    - Spotted Piggy Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 16)
      Brown, glazed, ceramic piggy bank with beige pots
    - Floral Piggy Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 6)
      Off-white, ceramic piggy bank with handle and yellow, green, and orange floral and geometric design
    - Change Purse Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 11)
      Pink, ceramic pig emerging through green change purse-shaped bank
    - Piggy Bank with Clover Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 18)
      Ceramic, pig-shaped bank with gold, clover motif; missing stopper
    - Piggy Bank with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 12)
      Pink, ceramic piggy bank with all over floral motif
    - Pig with Bucket Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 24)
      White, ceramic pig with reddish-brown shading with green and gold bucket that reads "Saving His Pennies, To Make, Mounds"
    - Spotted Piggy Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 7)
      Green, ceramic piggy bank with black and lighter green spots
    - Pig with Orange Features Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 8)
      White, ceramic pig with orange ears and tongue
    - Off-White, Floral Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 14)
      Off-white, ceramic, floral piggy bank with the word "Victory" across the back
    - Pig in Sailor Hat Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 1)
      Ceramic piggy bank in the shape of a brown pig wearing a sailor hat
    - Pigs on Seesaw Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 4)
      Ceramic bank in the shape of two pink pigs on seesaw on a bag of money with inscription "What Oh She Bumps 500,000" and clover detail; coin inside
    - Clear Piggy Bank, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 20)
      Clear, glass piggy bank
  - Subseries III I: Wall Hangings and Artwork
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed wall hangings and artwork in varied materials.
    - Clown Carrying a Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 9)
      Ceramic wall hanging of a human clown holding a pink pig in white clown outfit
    - Plaque of Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 11)
      Oval, wooden plaque depicting a pink pig outside; "Eat To Live, Don't Live To Eat" text across pig's back
    - Blue Pig Plate with Loose Hair, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 4)
      Blue, ceramic wall hanging with pink pig standing in the grass; packed with loose pig hair
    - Hollow Pig Wall Hanging, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 3)
      Clay pig wall hanging with hollow eyes, snout, and body
    - Pig in Top Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 22)
      Ceramic, pink pig in blue top hat wall hanging
    - Pig in Blue Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 11)
      Wall hanging of a pink pig with blue hat and tongue out
    - Pig and Floral Background, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 23)
      Framed, pink pig picture; floral background
  - Subseries III J: Ornaments
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed ornaments in varied materials.
    - Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 10)
      Bright orange, styrofoam pig ornament with blue, floral motif
    - Pig with Minimal Features, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 36)
      Green, minimal, wooden pig with floral design
    - Gray Pig with Orange, Yellow, and Green Pattern, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 76)
      Gray pig with orange, yellow, and green pattern; ornament
  - Subseries III K: Jewelry Containers
    This subseries contains multiple pig themed jewelry containers in varied materials.
    - Pig with Top Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 2)
      Ceramic, pink pig sitting next to a black, oversize top hat
    - Pig with Clover Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 7)
      White, ceramic container in the shape of a pig with clover motif
    - Pig in Coin Purse, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 13)
      Pink, ceramic pig in a blue coin purse with gold trim
    - Pig on Clover, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 11)
      Pink, ceramic pig sitting on green, clover-shaped jewelry tray
    - Pig with Pot, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 9)
      White, ceramic pig with white, ceramic pot
    - Pig with Large Bucket, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 13)
      Pink, ceramic pig sitting next to a green and orange, oversize bucket
    - Pig with Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 5)
      Off-white, ceramic pig in wood with log-like trough
    - Pigs on Bicycle with Baskets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 6)
      Three, off-white ceramic pigs in colored shirts riding a bicycle
    - Pig with Blue Trotters, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 7)
      White, ceramic pig with blue trotters
    - Pig with Sash, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 20)
      White pig with pink sash and brown ears and trotters
    - Pig with Lobster, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 13)
      Ceramic tray with lobster pinching the trotter of a pink pig
    - Pig with Banjo and Shoe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 3)
      Ceramic pig playing a banjo on a shoe with clover motifs
    - Pig Smoking a Pipe, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 6)
      Ceramic, pink pig smoking a pipe and resting in front of a stump and fence
    - Pig by Stump and Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 9)
      Pink, ceramic pig by tree stump kneeling on log-like trough
    - Pig Head Container, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 18)
      White and tan, ceramic pig head pot
    - Pig Sitting in Chair, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 8)
      Pink, ceramic pig in green chair
    - Pigs with Orange Features and Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 11)
      Three pink, ceramic pigs with orange eyes and snouts sitting on trough near mushrooms
    - Green and Gold Pig Tray, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 15)
      Gold, pig-shaped tray with green center for rings or other jewelry
    - Pig Head with Open Mouth, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 20)
      Green, ceramic pig head with open mouth
    - Pink Pig and Trough, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 21)
      Ceramic, pink pig straddling trough
    - Female Pig with Dinner Bell, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 23)
      Ceramic, female pig ringing a bell that reads "The Dinner Bell" for two peering over piglets
    - Yellowish Container with Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 3)
      Yellowish or beige pig container with three pigs on top